

### **PROFILE**

I am a 23 year old open-minded, independent, motivated Student at KEA. I am currently looking for a job where I can help to fulfil the companies ambitions within my area and my skills. I do speak German, English, Swedish and Norwegian.

## EXPERIENCE

#### KINDERGARDEN TEACHER

SVENSKA BARNDAGHEMMET I TAMMERFORS | APRIL 2018 - JULY 2018

### CHILDCARE SUPERVISOR

TUI GERMANY AS | MARCH 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2017

- planning and organising working schedules, weekly and monthly reports, motivating and leading a team of 12
- Highest guest satisfaction score on the whole island of Mallorca

#### STAGE ACTRESS IN " THE TALES OF HOFFMANN"

DE NORSKE OPERA OG BALLETT | OCTOBER 2013 - JAN 2015

## **EDUCATION**

### AP IN MULTIMEDIA DESIGN AND COMMUNICATION

KEA - KØBENHAVNS ENVERSAKADEMI | 2018 - 2020

# SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Languages: German, English, Norwegian, Swedish
- Mac and Microsoft Windows
- Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, XD, Premiere Pro, Audition CC
- excellent social and communication skills through my experience as waitress, entertainer
- blogging
- Acting, Dancing

### AWARDS

TUI GERMANY AS BEST TEAM PLAYER MARCH 2016